Prashant Soni



soniprashant9669@gmail.com

8878960680



Prashant Soni

I am a web designer with my 1Year 5 months of experience in creating beautiful and functional websites for various clients and projects. I have a strong knowledge of HTML, CSS, Bootstrap. I'm always eager to learn new skills and tools to enhance my web development process and deliver high-quality results. I'm also a team player who can collaborate effectively with other developers, designers, and stakeholders. My goal is to help you achieve your online goals with a website that reflects your brand and vision

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Cubexo Software Solution

Aug 2024 - Present

Frontend Developer

- Working as a Developed and maintained user-friendly web interfaces using HTML, CSS, Tailwind, Bootstrap, MUI, JavaScript and React.
- Collaborated with design and backend teams to implement responsive and interactive features.
- · Optimized web applications for maximum speed and scalability.
- Contributed to code reviews and maintained best practices in frontend development.

Alphawizz technologies Pvt. Ltd **Web Designer**

Nov 2023 - Aug 2024

- Working as a Developed and maintained user-friendly web interfaces using HTML, CSS, Bootstrap and JavaScript.
- Collaborated with design and backend teams to implement responsive and interactive features.
- Optimized web applications for maximum speed and scalability.
- Contributed to code reviews and maintained best practices in frontend development.

Jyoti Insulation

Oct 2021 - Jan 2023

Site Engineer

- · Managed and supervised construction projects, ensuring compliance with design specifications and safety standards.
- · Coordinated with subcontractors, suppliers, and stakeholders to maintain project timelines and budgets.
- · Conducted site inspections and assessments to identify potential issues and implement effective solutions.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Technology

2017 - 2021

Mahakal Institute of Technology and Managment, Ujjain

Higher Secondary (10+2)

2016 - 2017

Govt. Boys High Secondary School, Tarana

High School (10)

2014 - 2015

Sarswati Vidhya Mandir, Tarana

PROJECT

Shree Ramkinkar Vichar Mission

- Developed a spiritual website using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap.
- Created a responsive and visually appealing design to enhance user engagement.
- Implemented interactive features to improve user experience.

Alpha E-Commerce

Alpha E-Commerce is a cutting-edge multi-vendor e-commerce platform meticulously crafted by yours truly. With a focus on seamless user experience and robust functionality, Alpha E-Commerce empowers businesses to effortlessly set up their online storefronts, connect with customers, and drive sales. From intuitive product management to secure payment processing, Alpha E-Commerce delivers a comprehensive solution for thriving in the digital marketplace.

My Fuel

I developed a comprehensive online platform using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, and Bootstrap. This website allows users to book various services such as vehicle pickup, fuel delivery, and on-the-spot engine service

Many more....



Bootstrap —

CERTIFICATIONS

- · Front-End Web technologies (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap) by Universal informatics, Indore
- Front-End Web technologies (HTML, CSS, Bootstrap) Summer Training by Universal informatics, Ujjain
- · 2 Months Php internship from Eway It Solutions Ujjain
- Certified NX 10 (Unigraphics) course by SIEMENS it from three M software Private Limited, Ujjain
- Certified AutoCAD course by AUTODESK from Three M software Private Limited Ujjain

PERSONAL DETAILS

Name : Prashant Soni
Languages Known : English and Hindi
DOB : 25/05/1999

Address : 98, Kazi Chowk Tarana , Ujjain (M.P.)

I hereby declare that the above-mentioned information is correct up to my knowledge and I bear the responsibility for the correctness of the above-mentioned particulars.

Prashant Soni